{
    "id": "61353e73bffc44b4ac4988214e7fd4aa",
    "title": "Tag Questions",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "4ebc0cbf9d7c46efb7a95bfbb4d01e4e",
            "title": "Tag Questions",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Nothing was damaged during the storm, __________?",
                    "answers": [
                        "weren't they",
                        "were they",
                        "wasn't it",
                        "was it"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                },
                {
                    "question": "The news that they failed their driving test discouraged him, __________?",
                    "answers": [
                        "did they",
                        "didn't he",
                        "did it",
                        "didn't it"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                },
                {
                    "question": "If you had been strong, you'd have done it easily, __________?",
                    "answers": [
                        "had you",
                        "hadn't you",
                        "wouldn't you",
                        "would you"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Mrs. Black doesn't believe her son is able to draw such a picture, __________?",
                    "answers": [
                        "does he",
                        "doesn't he",
                        "does she",
                        "doesn't she"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He comes late sometimes, __________?",
                    "answers": [
                        "doesn't he",
                        "isn't he",
                        "comes he",
                        "he doesn't"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He failed to do anything last weekend, __________?",
                    "answers": [
                        "did he",
                        "didn't he",
                        "doesn't he",
                        "failed he"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We had to wait a long time to get our visa, _________?",
                    "answers": [
                        "don't we",
                        "didn't we",
                        "couldn't we",
                        "shouldn't we"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "What he said is impossible, __________?",
                    "answers": [
                        "wasn't it",
                        "was it",
                        "is it",
                        "isn't it"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                },
                {
                    "question": "This is the first time that your grandpa has been to America, __________?",
                    "answers": [
                        "isn't he",
                        "isn't it",
                        "hasn't he",
                        "has he"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The Smiths hardly ever go on travel, _________?",
                    "answers": [
                        "does he",
                        "doesn't he",
                        "do they",
                        "don't they"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}